Guide to the Liberty Hyde Bailey papers, 1845-2004
Bailey, Liberty Hyde papers, 1845-2004
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Macmillan and Publisher Correspondence, 1908 - 1963
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan.15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-28, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1923 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1923 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1924 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1924 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1924 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-19, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 20-30, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 192 (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 15-31, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1925 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan.15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-28, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan.15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-28, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan.15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-29, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1928 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1929 (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-28, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1929 (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1929 (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 104)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 105)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 106)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan.15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 107)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 108)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 15-28, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 109)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 110)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 111)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 112)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 15-30, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 113)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 114)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 115)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 116)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 15-30, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 117)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 118)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 119)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1-14 1930 (Box 32, Folder 120)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 121)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 122)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 15-30, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 123)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 124)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 125)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 126)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 15-30, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 127)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1-14, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 128)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 15-31, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 129)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1931 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1934 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1935 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1936 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1937 (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 81)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 82)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 83)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 84)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 85)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 86)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 87)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 88)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 89)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Oct. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 90)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 91)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1938 (Box 33, Folder 92)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 93)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Feb. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 94)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 95)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 96)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 97)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 98)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 99)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 100)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 101)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 102)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1939 (Box 33, Folder 103)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan. - Feb. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 104)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Mar. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 105)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Apr. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 106)
    - Macmillan Correspondence May, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 107)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 108)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jul. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 109)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Aug. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 110)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Sept. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 111)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Nov. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 112)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Dec. 1940 (Box 33, Folder 113)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1941 (Box 33, Folder 114)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1942 (Box 33, Folder 115)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1943 (Box 33, Folder 116)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1944 (Box 33, Folder 117)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1945 (Box 33, Folder 118)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1946 (Box 33, Folder 119)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1947 (Box 33, Folder 120)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jan - May 1948 (Box 33, Folder 121)
    - Macmillan Correspondence Jun. - Dec. 1948 (Box 33, Folder 122)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1949 (Box 33, Folder 123)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1950 (Box 33, Folder 124)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1951 (Box 33, Folder 125)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1952 (Box 33, Folder 126)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1953 (Box 33, Folder 127)
    - Macmillan Correspondence 1953-1963 (Box 33, Folder 128)
    - Contracts and Correspondence - Cyclopedia of Agriculture 1901 - 1913 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1885 - 1897 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1898 - 1899 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1902 - 1909 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1910 - 1914 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1915 - 1919 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1920 - 1930 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Contracts and Agreements 1931 - 1940 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Statements 1898 - 1939 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Statements 1941 - 1956 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Statements 1957 - 1970 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Publisher Correspondence - Statements 1971 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Publisher Correspondence - D. Margent Letters 1936 - 1937 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence 1946 - 1948 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Jan. 1939 - Mar. 1940 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Apr. 1940 - Oct. 1940 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Nov. 1940 - Feb. 1941 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Mar. 1941 - Apr. 1943 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, May 1943 - Mar. 1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Apr. 1945 - Sept. 1946 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, Jan. 1947 - Apr. 1948 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mc Farland Correspondence, May 1948 - Mar. 1949 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Contracts with MacMillan, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Letterbooks, 1894 - 1909
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: A - B, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: C - D, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: E - H, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: J - L, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: Macmillan, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: Macmillan - Munson, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: N - S, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Letterbook "1" Correspondence: T - W, 1894 - May 1896 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: A - C, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: D - G, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: H - L, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: Macmillan, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: Macmillan - Mead, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Letterbook "2" Correspondence: N - Y, June 1896 - Mar. 19, 1898 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: A - D, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: E - J, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: K - L, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: Macmillan, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: Macmillan - Munson, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: N - S, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Letterbook "3" Correspondence: T - W, Mar. 20, 1898 - Mar. 1900 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Letterbook "4" Correspondence: A - C, Apr. 1900 - Feb. 1901 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Letterbook "4" Correspondence: D - G, Apr. 1900 - Feb. 1901 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Letterbook "4" Correspondence: H - L, Apr. 1900 - Feb. 1901 (Box 25, Folder 24)